{"data":[{"question":"The basic law of addition, subtraction, multiplication and division are taught to all elementary school students.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"law","b":"division","c":"taught","d":"school","answer":"1","explain":" - Law-> laws","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"A largely percentage of Canadian export business is with the United States.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"largely","b":"of","c":"is","d":"with","answer":"1","explain":" - Largely-> large","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"The famous Jim Thorpe won both the pentathlon or decathlon in the 1912 Olympic Games.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The famous","b":"won","c":"or","d":"in","answer":"3","explain":" - or-> and","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"Acute pharyngitis pain is most often caused by a viral infection, for who antibiotics are ineffective.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is","b":"caused by","c":"who","d":"are ineffective","answer":"3","explain":" - For who-> for which","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"Knowledges about cultures provides insights into the learned behaviors of groups.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Knowledges","b":"insights into","c":"learned","d":"behaviors","answer":"1","explain":" - Knowledges-> knowledge","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"A fiber-optic cable across the Pacific went into service in April 1989, link the United States and Japan.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"across","b":"went into","c":"in","d":"link","answer":"4","explain":" - Link-> linked","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"Dislike the gorilla, the make adult chimpanzee weighs under 200 pounds.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Dislike","b":"make","c":"under","d":"pounds","answer":"1","explain":" - Dislike-> unlike","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"Before lumberjacks and mechanical equipments, they used horses and ropes to drag lops.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Before","b":"equipments","c":"used","d":"to drag","answer":"2","explain":" - Equipments-> Equipment","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"George Gershwin not only composed popular songs for musicals, also wrote more serious concerts.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"composed","b":"for","c":"also","d":"more serious","answer":"3","explain":" \n- Also-> but also","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"Among the world's 44 richest countries there has been not war since 1945.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Among the","b":"richest","c":"there","d":"not","answer":"4","explain":" - Not-> no","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"}]}